https://www.trivita.com/privacy-policy/

Brought to you by:
Privacy Policy
The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you about what information may be collected from you when visiting our web site (“Web Site”), how such information will be used, with whom such information may be shared, your ability to edit, update, correct or delete such information and the security procedures that we have implemented to protect your privacy.
Collection & Use of Information:
When visiting our Web Site, you may be asked for certain types of personally identifiable information (e.g., your first and last name, mailing address, city, state, zip code, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card number, etc.). This information allows us to administer our business, better provide products and services to you, communicate offers on products that may be of interest to you or to others disclosed by you, and to fulfill your order. You may volunteer to disclose personally identifiable information to us. If you do not want to disclose your personally identifiable information to us, please do not submit it. We may also collect non-personally identifiable information from you when you visit the Web Site (e.g., your IP address, browser type, domain name, etc.). This information is collected and analyzed in the aggregate in order to improve the function and content of the Web Site.
As noted above, we use the information that is collected about you for a variety of purposes, such as confirming and fulfilling your order, adding you to our e-mail newsletter subscription list, analyzing trends and statistics, improving the operation of the Web Site, sending informational and promotional materials, and to help us design and enhance our products and services offerings so that we may provide you with quality products, services and superior customer support.
We may disclose the information that we collect about you when we have reason to believe that it is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against persons or entities that may be causing injury to you, to us or to others. We may also disclose information to assist in compliance with certain laws and regulations.
Affiliate Members and Vendors:
We have existing business relationships and may develop other relationships in the future (hereinafter, “Affiliate Members”). In these instances, we may share or otherwise allow access to information that is collected about you that will enable our Affiliate Members to contact you regarding products and services that may be of interest. We may employ vendors to perform functions on our behalf. Examples may include fulfilling orders, preparing mailings, delivering packages, e-mail administrative functions, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. These vendors are under contractual obligation to use confidential data only for those purposes for which they are hired.
Protection of Children:
Our Web Site is a general audience site that is not specifically designed or targeted at children. We do not knowingly collect, use or disseminate any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If, however, we become aware that personally identifiable information regarding a child under the age of 13 has been collected on the Web Site, we will use such information for the sole purpose of contacting a parent or guardian of the child to obtain verifiable parental consent. If we cannot obtain consent after a reasonable period of time, or if when contacted a parent or guardian requests that we do not use or maintain such information, we will make reasonable efforts to delete it from our records. Upon request by a parent or guardian, TriVita will provide a description of the specific types of personal information collected from a child who is under the age of 13.
Cookies:
A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a web site’s computers which is stored on your computer’s hard drive. Each web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it. However, to protect your privacy, your browser permits a web site to access only those cookies it sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other websites. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. Each browser is different, so check the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.
If you reject all cookies, you will not be able to use TriVita services that require you to “log on,” and you may not be able to take full advantage of all offerings. However, there may be some TriVita products and services that do not require that you accept cookies.
TriVita uses its own cookies for a number of purposes, including to:
Access your information when you “log on,” so that we can provide you with customized content in certain online areas; Conduct research to improve TriVita content and services; and Require you to re-enter your Access Code after a certain period of time has elapsed to help protect you against others accidentally accessing your account contents. Please note that TriVita does not control the use or contents of third-party cookies.
Third-Party Links:
In an attempt to provide increased value to our visitors, TriVita may choose various third-party websites to link to from TriVita’s Web Site. However, even if the third party is affiliated with TriVita, TriVita has no control over these linked sites, each of which may (or may not) have their own privacy policies and practices in place. Any information you provide to third-party websites will be governed under the terms of each web site’s privacy policy and we encourage you to investigate and ask questions before disclosing any information to the operators of third-party websites. TriVita has no responsibility or liability whatsoever for the content, actions or policies of third-party websites. The inclusion of third-party websites on our Web Site in no way constitutes an endorsement of such web site’s content, actions or policies. These linked sites are for your convenience and you access them at your own risk.
Nonetheless, TriVita seeks to protect the integrity of its Web Site and the links placed upon it. Therefore, TriVita requests any feedback not only on its own website, but for sites it links to as well (including if a specific link does not work).
Access or Corrections to Your Information:
If you identify any inaccuracy in your personal information, or you need to make a change or would like to verify such information, please contact us so that we may update our records. Our contact information is set forth below. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to accommodate all such requests.
Security:
TriVita has implemented a number of security measures to help protect your information. Your information is stored on secured networks consistent with industry standards, and is accessible by those employees and agents who have special access rights to such systems. When you access account information, we offer the use of a secure server. Industry-standard encryption technologies are used when transferring or receiving sensitive information supplied by users. While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee or warrant its complete security. No data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. We shall not be responsible for harm that you or any person may suffer as a result of a breach of confidentiality in respect to your use of our Web Site or any information you transmit to our Web Site.
Modifications to Policy:
We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy, along with any related provisions, at any time. Any changes to this Agreement will be effective immediately upon notice, which may be provided to you via e-mail or by posting the latest version on our Web Site (hereinafter, “Notice”). Your use of the Web Site after such Notice will be deemed acceptance of such changes. Be sure to review this Privacy Policy periodically to ensure familiarity with its most current version. You can easily confirm whether any revisions have been posted since your last visit by checking the date on which the Policy was last revised, which is set forth at the top of this Policy. If you object to such changes, we will honor our prior privacy policies as to any data previously collected. If you disagree with the changes in our policy, however, please do not use the Web Site after the posting of such changes online. By using the Web Site following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy, you agree to all such changes.
Questions or Comments or to Contact Us:
If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, or you wish to access or make changes to information about you, please call TriVita at 1-877-850-2968 or write us at:
TriVita, Inc.
